

Name          : PackageManagement
Author        : Microsoft Corporation
Version       : 1.2.4
PublishedDate : 01/12/2018 03:01:27
Repository    : PSGallery
Description   : PackageManagement (a.k.a. OneGet) is a new way to discover and install software packages from around 
                the web.
                 It is a manager or multiplexor of existing package managers (also called package providers) that 
                unifies Windows package management with a single Windows PowerShell interface. With PackageManagement, 
                you can do the following.
                  - Manage a list of software repositories in which packages can be searched, acquired and installed
                  - Discover software packages
                  - Seamlessly install, uninstall, and inventory packages from one or more software repositories



