

Name          : Pester
Author        : Pester Team
Version       : 4.6.0
PublishedDate : 21/01/2019 19:52:53
Repository    : PSGallery
Description   : Pester provides a framework for running BDD style Tests to execute and validate PowerShell commands 
                inside of PowerShell and offers a powerful set of Mocking Functions that allow tests to mimic and mock 
                the functionality of any command inside of a piece of PowerShell code being tested. Pester tests can 
                execute any command or script that is accessible to a pester test file. This can include functions, 
                Cmdlets, Modules and scripts. Pester can be run in ad hoc style in a console or it can be integrated 
                into the Build scripts of a Continuous Integration system.



